storeblogs.com 2013-12-06

# StoreBlogs » Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy

We want the StoreBlogs network, community and services to be built on trust and pledge to remain committed to maintaining the privacy of any StoreBlogs member or website user. This website privacy policy ( _the_ “ _Privacy Policy_ “) is meant to inform you about the practices for gathering, storing and disseminating information collected Online, or through the use of our website ( _the_ “ _Site_ “) and how we use, or intend to use, that information.

By using the StoreBlogs platform, network, community and services and by accessing the StoreBlogs Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy set forth below, we urge you to refrain from using or accessing the Site, network, community or services. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as outlined below. The Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time by us without notice. All changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy and we encourage you to check back here periodically for any policy updates or changes.

## 1\. Information Collection.

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell or disclose information that identifies users of the StoreBlogs network personally or makes it possible for other parties to contact them directly (“ _Personal Information_ “). We also collect non-personal information (“ _Anonymous Information_ “), such as pages visited, on the StoreBlogs network Site. We may also collect or develop aggregated information, which may include Anonymous Information and Personal Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you or any of our other users (“ _Aggregated Information_ “).

**a. Voluntarily Information.**

When you register to list your blog within the StoreBlogs network, order goods or services from the Site, or register for our newsletter, we will collect and retain information about you, some of which is Personal Information. For example, registration requires you to provide a valid e-mail address, your username, first name, last name, city and country. This e-mail address provided by you in the registration form will only be used and disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Any other information you provide in your user profile will be visible to others, including anonymous visitors to the Site. If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply. When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information. We may also collect Personal Information, such as demographic information, from you at other points on the Site that state that Personal Information is being collected.

**b. Cookies.**

We collect Anonymous Information about you and your use of the StoreBlogs network, community and services whenever you visit us online. This includes use of cookies to store your user session IDs. StoreBlogs uses session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. StoreBlogs does not use cookies to track your web browsing on other websites.

**c. Visitor Tracking.**

As is true of most websites, StoreBlogs gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movements around the Site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Except as noted herein, we do not link this automatically-collected data to Personal Information.

**d. IP Addresses.**

Each user’s IP address is logged with each visit and each action performed on the Site. This information is never provided to third parties, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, and is logged only for a temporary period of time. IP address information is linked to Personal Information and may be used in an effort to block a “banned” user from accessing the Site.

**e. Advertising.**

If there is advertising on the Site, such advertising may employ the use of cookies or other methods to track hits and click-throughs. We are not responsible for advertiser cookies or how the information gathered through their use might be used.

**f. Public Websites.**

You should be aware that any Personal Information you submit on the Site in blogs, comments, other posts and your member profile can be read, collected, or used by other users of this Site, including anonymous visitors, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit or share on this Site or within your member profile.

**g. Aggregated Information.**

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all Aggregated Information. When we share such information with other companies, it is not traceable to any particular user, and will not be used to contact you.

## 2\. Information Use.

**a. Personal Information Use.**

In general, Personal Information you submit is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. StoreBlogs may use your Personal Information in the following ways: to facilitate the creation of and secure your account on our blog network; to identify you as a user on our platform or within our system; to provide improved administration of our Site and services; to improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Site; to send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your account was created; to send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories; to respond to your inquiries or other requests; to send promotional communications; to provide you with electronic newsletters, or surveys; to send and facilitate upgrades and special offers related to our services and for other marketing purposes, should you request to receive such communications from us. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly. Should you decide to opt-out of receiving future mailings, we may share your e-mail address with third parties to ensure that you do not receive further communications from third parties. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to this Privacy Policy.

**b. Anonymous and Aggregated Information Use.**

We may create Anonymous Information and Aggregated Information from Personal Information by excluding information ( _such as your name_ ) that make the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Information and Aggregated Information so that we may enhance the quality of our Site and services and improve the Site usability or design. StoreBlogs reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information and Aggregated Information to third parties in its discretion.

**c. Feedback Use.**

If you provide feedback on our Site or in regards to any of our services, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. StoreBlogs will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Information in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## 3\. Information Disclosure.

**a. Co-branded Services.**

At some point, we may share Anonymous or Aggregated Information with certain businesses with which StoreBlogs has formed a strategic alliance. You may be able to identify these businesses because Storeblogs has authorized them to display clearly identified and branded images on the Storeblogs network, community or service pages and in its communications. These strategic partners are requested to clearly state their own privacy policies on their own websites or promotional materials, and if you provide them with your Personal Information, it may become subject to the policies of the respective company. StoreBlogs may receive information from these strategic partners and may add such information to information already collected from you. No Personal Information identifiable to a specific user is collected or shared with these strategic partners from the StoreBlogs network, community or services.

**b. Third Party Services.**

StoreBlogs reserves the right to offer third party services and products to you on the Site, such as via newsletters or special offers. We may share Aggregated Information about our user base with other entities, such as advertisers. This information does not identify individual users, except where you have given us prior, specific permission to do so. We do not link Aggregated Information with Personal Information. We may share Personal Information with third-party vendors and partners only in those situations where you have given us prior, specific permission to do so.

**c. Third Party Contractors.**

We may share your Personal Information with third party contractors or service providers to provide you with the services that we offer you though our Site; to conduct quality assurance testing; to facilitate creation of accounts; to provide help or support; or to provide specific services in accordance with your instructions. These third parties are required not to use your Personal Information other than to provide the services requested by StoreBlogs. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Information with our contractors and third party service providers for the sole purpose of providing services to you.

**d. Affiliates.**

StoreBlogs is currently a subsidiary of Visible.net, Inc. ( _the_ “ _Parent_ “). At this time there are no other subsidiaries, joint ventures, parent companies, or other companies under a common control ( _collectively_ , “ _Affiliates_ “) associated with the StoreBlogs Site, network, community or services. Additional Affiliates may be added here in the future. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with these Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by it and StoreBlogs and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**e. Legal Requirements.**

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect or defend our rights, property, or users and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on StoreBlogs.

## 4\. Third Party Links.

StoreBlogs contains links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by StoreBlogs. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects Personal Information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by, from or within this Site.

## 5\. Security.

StoreBlogs is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Despite these measures, you should know that StoreBlogs cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information and mistakes may happen.

## 6\. Dispute Resolution.

If you believe that StoreBlogs has not adhered to the Privacy Policy, please contact StoreBlogs by e-mail at help@storeblogs.com. We will do our best to address your concerns. If you feel that your complaint has been addressed incompletely, we invite you to let us know for further investigation.

## 7\. Personal Information Changes.

You may change any of your Personal Information by editing your profile or by sending an e-mail to StoreBlogs at help@storeblogs.com. You may request deletion of your Personal Information by StoreBlogs, but please note that we may be required ( _by law or otherwise_ ) to keep this information and not delete it ( _or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements_ ). When we delete the account information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our system or data archives.

## 4\. Privacy Policy Updates.

If we decide to make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Site. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on the Site. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use or disclosure of Personal Information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use or disclosure of your Personal Information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of our services and access to the StoreBlogs network, community or services following notice of such changes, shall indicate your acknowledgment of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

## 5\. Additional Information.

If you have any additional questions about any information contained within the StoreBlogs Privacy Policy, or about using the Site, or information about StoreBlogs in general, please contact StoreBlogs using one of the following methods:

StoreBlogs  
14953 N.E. 95th Street  
Redmond, WA 98052

Phone: (888) 820-5383  
E-mail: [contact@storeblogs.com](mailto:contact@storeblogs.com "StoreBlogs Contact")

Questions about our policies can also be sent using our [contact form](http://storeblogs.com/contact#contact-form "Contact Us").

## 18\. Additional Terms.

Please take the time to review our Additional Terms:

By using the Site, you agree that you have read and that your adequately comprehend all Site policies, including the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.
